<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<recipes>
  <recipe name="Sunshine Toast">
    <summary>
      This is a quick easy recipe, for lovers of fried eggs on toast. It's a clever twist on usual fried eggs.
    </summary>
    <categories>
      <category name="Dishes and Meals/Trusted Brands: Recipes and Tips/American Egg Board" />
      <category name="Breakfast and Brunch/Egg Dishes" />
      <category name="Everyday Cooking/Quick and Easy" />
      <category name="Bread" />
      <category name="Breakfast and Brunch " />
    </categories>
    <timing prepTime="15" cookTime="10" totalTime="15" />
    <nutricialPerServing calories="342" totalFatGrams="28.8" CholesterolMilligrams="273" />
    <ingredients servings="1">
      <ingredient name="butter" quantity="30" unit="grams" />
      <ingredient name="bread" quantity="1" unit="slice" />
      <ingredient name="egg" quantity="1" unit="item" />
      <ingredient name="salt" quantity="1" unit="item" />
    </ingredients>
    <steps>
      <step>
        Melt 1 tablespoon butter in a small skillet over medium heat.
      </step>
      <step>
        Using a glass or cookie cutter, create a hole in the middle of the bread, removing the center so it is perfectly circular. 
        Butter the bread lightly on both sides and lightly fry it on one side, and then turn it over. Crack the egg into the hole in the middle 
        of the bread and fry quickly. Be careful that the bread does not burn. Serve warm.
      </step>
    </steps>
    <reviews>
      <review rating="5" user="sarahjo" date="27-06-2008" valued="108">
        This was made for my sister and I when we were little, only we called it "Toad in the Hole". 
        I made this today for my boys, just to make today a little easier. I used a star cookie cutter and after the egg cooked a little, 
        I put a little shredded cheese on the egg before flipping. I like mine with hot sauce and sometimes salsa to dip. 
        My boys LOVED these, and asked for seconds! Thanks for posting this recipe. It's nice to share these recipes I had as a kid 
        with my boys."/>
      </review>
      <review rating="5" user="leenie050" date="16-11-2007" valued="104">
        We call it egg-in-a-hole, and I have perfected the art! First, it helps to cook on a low heat and cover with a lid to cook 
        the egg without burning the bread. Also, I sprinkle salt pepper and Season-all on the raw egg side. Second, after you flip 
        the bread to cook the other side, sprinkle a little cheddar cheese on the cooked side and cover again and allow cheese to melt 
        while the other side cooks. Hope you love the suggestions!
      </review>
    </reviews>
  </recipe>
  <recipe name="Shrimp and Broccoli Fettuccine">
    <summary>
      Fettuccine with garlic shrimp and broccoli in a lemony cream sauce is topped with chopped fresh tomatoes in this easy 
      but elegant one-dish meal
    </summary>
    <categories>
      <category name="Everyday Cooking/Quick and Easy/30-Minute-Meals" />
      <category name="Pasta" />
    </categories>
    <timing prepTime="20" totalTime="20" />
    <nutricialPerServing calories="308" totalFatGrams="10.6" CholesterolMilligrams="14" />
    <ingredients servings="4">
      <ingredient name="fettuccine, uncooked" quantity="0.25" unit="pounds" />
      <ingredient name="broccoli florets" quantity="1" unit="cup" />
      <ingredient name="frozen cooked cleaned medium shrimp, thawed" quantity="0.75" unit="pounds" />
      <ingredient name="clove garlic, minced" quantity="1" unit="item" />
      <ingredient name="tub PHILADELPHIA Savory Lemon &amp; Herb Cooking Creme" quantity="10" unit="ounce" />
      <ingredient name="milk" quantity="0.25" unit="cup" />
      <ingredient name="chopped tomatoes" quantity="0.25" unit="cup" />
    </ingredients>
    <steps>
      <step>
        Cook pasta in large saucepan as directed on package, omitting salt and adding broccoli for the last 3 min. Drain; keep warm.
      </step>
      <step>
        Cook and stir shrimp and garlic in large nonstick skillet on medium heat 2 to 3 min. or until shrimp are heated through. Add 
        cooking creme and milk; cook and stir 2 min.
      </step>
      <step>
        Add pasta to shrimp mixture; mix lightly. Top with tomatoes.
      </step>
    </steps>
    <servingSuggestion>
      Serve with a mixed green salad tossed with your favorite KRAFT Light Dressing.
    </servingSuggestion>
    <variations>
      <variation>
        Prepare as directed, substituting 3/4 lb. boneless skinless chicken breasts, cut into strips, for the shrimp and 
        increasing the cooking time to 6 to 7 min. or until chicken is done. Add cooking creme and milk; continue as directed.
      </variation>
    </variations>
    <reviews>
      <review rating="4" user="jharvey0507" date="17-02-2012" valued="19">
        I made this and it is DELICIOUS! I did add a couple things. I sauteed the shrimp and garlic in butter instead of simply 
        alone in the pan, that kept them from sticking and it added a touch of flavor. Also, I DID NOT omit the salt when boiling 
        the fetuccine. It made a difference in the flavor, but a good difference. Next time I will add chicken boulion to the water 
        instead to add more depth to the flavor though, and maybe even put a bit in the cooking cream mixture, it just seemed like 
        it needed something else. But if you don't like robust flavors, I wouldn't suggest it. I like to take recipe's, change them up
        and make them my own. I WAS DELICIOUS AS IT WAS ANYWAY!!!!
      </review>
      <review rating="4" user="N. Huffer" date="17-02-2012" valued="15">
        I went to several different grocery stores and could not find the lemon pepper cooking cream. I had to settle for Italian 
        Cheese instead. But it was a Valentine's Day delight for the husband. Thanks for the quick and easy recipe. There was too 
        much sauce that never really thickened up. I just steamed more broccoli and added it- perfect.
      </review>
    </reviews>
  </recipe>
</recipes>